

# José Manuel Aguza Barragán

Software engineer



### **RESUMEN**

Hello! I am José Manuel Aguza Barragán. I am a Software Engineer specialized in web development, currently working for the multinational Everis.

I was born on June 19, 1998 in en El Pedroso but right now I reside in Seville (Spain). I started my studies in Computer Engineering - Software Engineering in 2016, at Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería Informática at the University of Seville.

I have a B driving licence and my own vehicle, as well as availability to travel and flexible working hours.





(+34) 672102851



jmaguzab@gmail.com



My website with extra information about me here.



You can found my LinkedIn here.



Calle Tarfia número 47 bajo derecha







## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Solution Assistant**

15/03/2021 - today

Everis

I am currently working as a Solution assistant for the multinational company Everis, specifically I offer my services for Everis Seville.

My position in the projects in which I work is junior developer.

#### Researcher and developer

15/09/2020 - 15/03/2021

Ingeniería Web y Testing Temprano

I worked for 6 months in the research industry developing tasks related to robotic process automation (RPA) and artificial intelligence (AI) for the research group of the niversity of Seville IWT2 in collaboration with the Servinform company.

I decided to leave this position to explore new challenges outside the research field.



## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

### Computer Engineering - Software Engineering

University of Seville

19/09/2016 - 01/03/2021

I finished my degree in Software Engineering in the first semester of 2021. I obtained an average of 8.18 with 5 distinctions marks and a mark of 9 in the final degree project.

#### English level B1

2020

Cambridge

I have the english level B1 certificate by Cambridge.

### High school diploma with specialization in technology

I.E.S. San Fernando, Constantina (Sevilla)

2014 - 2016

I studied Science and Technology modality, in which I obtained 9,3 as an average mark.

## E

## **FURTHER INFORMATION**

If you would like to know more about me, such as the different technologies I have worked, my skills or the projects I have been involved in, please visit my website: <a href="https://aguza5.github.io/CV/">https://aguza5.github.io/CV/</a>